livesmarterdaily.com 2016-11-19

# Proven Advice To Save You Money On Your Car Insurance Bill

Get Auto Insurance Quotes 

## Privacy Policy

Effective date August 5, 2016 

### Introduction

EverQuote DBA AdHarmonics (herein referred to as "we", "us" or "our") considers your privacy a very important issue. We design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy as a primary concern. 

This privacy policy (the "Policy") applies to our website, livesmarterdaily.com (the "Site") and outlines the types of information we collect via the Site, how we use that information, and the efforts we make to safeguard it. By providing any information through the Site, you agree to the use of that information consistent with this Policy. 

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website livesmarterdaily.com and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile application. 

### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information ("PII") is information that identifies you, is not generally available to the public and may include information about your family as well as you personally. We collect the PII that you provide us via the Site so that we may provide you with the service(s) we offer. If you elect, we may also collect PII from third-party data providers. You are not obligated to provide us with PII; however, if you do not provide us with certain information that we request, we may not be able to respond to your requests, process your applications or otherwise conduct the business contemplated between you and us. 

For example, in order to provide you with insurance quotes, we collect your personal contact information including name, telephone number, mailing address, email address, gender, birthday, marital status, information about your vehicles and drivers and may also collect information about your credit and your existing insurance coverage. 

If you are an insurance agent using EverQuote Pro to purchase referrals, we work with a third-party to collect from you and transmit your credit card and billing information. Your credit card number and related information are not accessible by us. 

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts or similar technologies are used by EverQuote and our partners, including our marketing partners, affiliates, and analytic service providers (e.g. Google Analytics). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

When you visit our site, we also capture the user agent string from your device which helps us classify the type of device you are using to interact with the Site (e.g. desktop, tablet, mobile device). The user agent string does not, however, collect any personally identifiable information. 

We use cookies for a variety of reasons, including to remember user settings (e.g. zip code, address, kind of auto). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

In addition, we partner with third parties to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

Further, we serve display advertising utilizing our ad serving infrastructure. This infrastructure uses cookies, web beacons, images, and scripts to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites for the purpose of providing the best user experience with our advertisements. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [this link](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

### Use of Information

  * By submitting your e-mail address and/or phone number (as the case may be) via this Site, you authorize us to use that e-mail address and phone number to contact you periodically, via e-mail and manually-dialed and/or auto-dialed telephone calls, concerning (i) your quote requests, (ii) any administrative issue regarding the Site or our services and/or (iii) information or offers that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also send e-mails to you periodically regarding updated quotes. You may opt out of receiving e-mails from us at any time by unsubscribing as set forth in the applicable e-mail. 

  * Additionally, by filling out information on this Site as part of your request for information about insurance policies and quotations, you authorize us to provide that information to various insurance companies, insurance agents and other related third parties that participate in our insurance quote network (collectively "Insurance Providers"). The Insurance Providers may provide your personal information to their insurance carriers, suppliers and other related vendors in order to generate price quotations and information relevant to insurance policies that you have requested, and the Insurance Providers may use the contact information (including telephone number(s)) you have provided to contact you directly with quotations by means of telephone (manually or auto-dialed), fax, email and postal mail, even if you have registered your phone number(s) on local and/or national no-call lists. You further acknowledge and agree that each Insurance Provider that receives your quote request from this website or from our affiliates may confirm your information through the use of a consumer report, which may include among other things, your driving record and/or credit score. For purposes of faxing, it is understood that Insurance Providers have an established business relationship with each user of this website, if required to comply with the then current law. 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove it by making the change on our member information page [or by emailing our Customer Support at compliance@adharmonics.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 10 business days. 

We will retain your information for as long as required to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the Insurance Providers are obligated to protect your PII to at least the degree established in this Policy. Additionally, it is our policy to require Insurance Providers to use commercially reasonable means to secure the receipt and processing of your PII. You should be aware, however, that after an Insurance Provider contacts you directly, any information you provide directly to the Insurance Provider, which may be the same as or similar to the PII you submitted to us through this Site, will no longer be covered by this Policy. Before providing your information directly to an individual Insurance Provider, you should make sure that you have read and understand that Insurance Provider's privacy policies and practices. We have no control over the Insurance Providers and their practices and we are not and will not be responsible or liable, financially or otherwise, for their respective privacy policies and practices. Also, be aware that the Insurance Providers may use the PII they acquire from this Site in connection with other information they acquire about you (from other sources that have collected PII about you such as credit reporting companies, etc.) as well as information you provide them directly. We are not and will not be responsible or liable, financially or otherwise, for any of the PII that you provide directly to any Insurance Provider or that they acquire from sources other than this Site. In addition, if you no longer want to receive communications from the Insurance Providers regarding insurance quotes, you must contact the respective Insurance Provider(s) directly and request that they no longer contact you. You may not opt out of communications from any Insurance Provider by contacting us. 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. 

We may also share your PII with the following types of entities and/or under the following circumstances: 

  * We may share your information with third parties with whom we have promotional or advertising relationships (provided that we are not otherwise restricted from this sharing of information). If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at compliance@adharmonics.com. 
  * We may provide your PII to, or permit access to it by, our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, vendors and/or service providers, such as our ISP or infrastructure hosting companies, for the purpose of processing such information and/or contacting you on our behalf, or where such access is incidental to their providing assistance to us. In such cases, we expect these parties to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 
  * At some point, we may establish subsidiaries or other related companies, or merge with or be acquired by another company. Should that happen, then we may disclose your information to them, in which case we will request that they abide by this Policy. We may also disclose some information to a potential acquirer, although such disclosure would be subject to normal and customary requirements. In the event we are acquired, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 
  * We reserve the right to disclose your PII as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a court order, legal process or judicial proceeding served on us. 

### Opt-out

If you no longer desire to receive communications from us, you may opt-out by emailing our Customer Support at compliance@adharmonics.com or by contacting us by postal mail at AdHarmonics, 210 Broadway, Suite 302, Cambridge, MA 02139. 

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us and we take commercially reasonable precautions in an effort to safeguard it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at compliance@adharmonics.com. 

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. If you provide a testimonial to us, you agree that we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at compliance@adharmonics.com. 

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Changes in this Policy

If we change our privacy practices, we will post a revised version of the Policy on this Site and the revised Policy will be effective when posted. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review the Site frequently for any changes. By continuing to use the services or the Site after the revised Policy is posted, you will be deemed to have been made aware of and to have accepted, and you will be subject to, such amended or revised Policy. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. By continuing to use the services or the Site after the revised Policy is posted, you will be deemed to have been made aware of and to have accepted, and you will be subject to, such amended or revised Policy. 

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first send an email to compliance@adharmonics.com. You may also contact us via regular mail at: AdHarmonics, 210 Broadway, Suite 302, Cambridge, MA 02139. If you would prefer to contact us via phone, please call (855) 522-3444
